<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wallpaper Background</title>
    <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wallpaper Background</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, [Get Update](https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reese Peanut Butter Cups Pie</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/reese-peanut-butter-cups-pie.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/reese-peanut-butter-cups-pie.html</guid>
      <description>If peanut allergies are a concern, these treats can be made using a variety of nut. The united states customary cup holds 8 fluid ounces. Find out which peanut butter cup stole our hearts. When i just have to have something sweet, this is it, and it&amp;#039;s not too fattening. we may earn commission from links on this page, but we only recommend products we back. Mornings are about to get pretty sweet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rsbn Live</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/rsbn-live.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/rsbn-live.html</guid>
      <description>Practice is certainly important, but without applying it to real action. If undetected or untreated, this can cause irreversible damage to the eye. If you have glaucoma, you know that the main goal is to prevent damage to the optic nerve. Of these individuals, 253,768,092 were adults that were 18 years old or older. Tiktok might be all about songs, viral dances, pranks, comedy bits and everything in between, but for those in the know, it’s also a platform that’s perfect for hopping on the craze of streaming in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Is Julius Jones</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/who-is-julius-jones.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/who-is-julius-jones.html</guid>
      <description>Julius darius jones (born july 25, 1980) is an american man on death row in oklahoma who was convicted of the july 1999 murder of businessman paul scott . A parole board is recommending clemency for julius jones who was convicted and sentenced to death for a crime he said he did not commit. On july 31st, julius jones was arrested and charged with the murder of paul howell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Fire</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/colorado-fire.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/colorado-fire.html</guid>
      <description>The pilot of an air tanker was killed tuesday when the plane crashed near a part of colorado where crews have been battling a wildfire, . Northwest colorado fire unit in craig, upper colorado river . In 2012, drought and extreme weather fueled the waldo canyon fire, which was the largest recorded wildfire in colorado&amp;#039;s history at the time. 31940 likes · 15 talking about this. Steep terrain, large areas of continuous fuels and frequent high fire danger weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Live Youtube</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-live-youtube.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-live-youtube.html</guid>
      <description>The national guard is activated in kenosha, wisconsin and the governor has authorized 500 troops to support local law enforcement in . Subscribe to livenow from fox! From the wisconsin streets where kyle rittenhouse shot three people. The homicide trial of kyle rittenhouse resumed on tuesday with the defendant picking the names of the 12 jurors who will decide his fate. Signup for outkick vip by clicking here, .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tornadoes Long Island</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/tornadoes-long-island.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/tornadoes-long-island.html</guid>
      <description>Our editors independently research, test, and recommend the best products; In the hgtv series &amp;#039;renovation island,&amp;#039; contractor bryan baeumler and his wife sarah move their family to the undeveloped south andros island, bahamas, to restore a rundown beach resort. Researchers continue to develop techno. Rd.com true stories survival stories the voorhes for reader&amp;#039;s digest on the day the tornado hit, there was no indication severe weather was on its way—the sky was blue and the sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rittenhouse Trial Live Update</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/rittenhouse-trial-live-update.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/rittenhouse-trial-live-update.html</guid>
      <description>The decorating experts at hgtv share 30 tips for creatively updating your living room for almost no cost. Don&amp;#039;t let a barely there budget keep you from creating a room you&amp;#039;ll love living in. A preliminary competition or test to determine qualifications. We&amp;#039;re rescheduling the 2020 fair. The minecraft suite of games is getting new additions, said developer mojang during a mine.
  82zyhsul2v2xm from static.independent.co.uk  ©rustic white photography ©rustic white photography ©rustic white photography ©rustic white photography ©.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copper</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/copper.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/copper.html</guid>
      <description>We may earn commission from links on this page, but we only recommend products we back. Hi, i’m a 15 year old kid who likes to work with wood and metal. Leaky pipes are not only a nuisance but are also a potential source of major plumbing trouble, so it makes sense to nip the issue in the bud and fix it asap. While there are a lot of dupes out there that only look like copper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November Full Moon Lunar Eclipse</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/november-full-moon-lunar-eclipse.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/november-full-moon-lunar-eclipse.html</guid>
      <description>We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy. Why not brush up on your lunar eclipse knowledge beforehand? Here&amp;#039;s what you need to know about it. All about the astrological moon: Brush up on your facts before the next one appears in the sky.
  Pm2izcucvkqjm from starwalk.space  Early tomorrow morning (wednesday, october 8), a total lunar eclipse &amp;#039;blood moon&amp;#039; will be visible from north america, east asia,.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julio Lugo</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/julio-lugo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/julio-lugo.html</guid>
      <description>Lugo was drafted by the houston astros in 1994 and eventually played in the mlb for 12 seasons. Espn reported that the cause of death was presumed to be a heart attack, citing lugo’s family. 2 days ago · julio lugo, longtime mlb shortstop who won a world series with the boston red sox, has died, the family told enrique rojas of espn. November 16, 1975 in barahona, dominican republic do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rittenhouse Trial Live Youtube</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/rittenhouse-trial-live-youtube.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/rittenhouse-trial-live-youtube.html</guid>
      <description>Live court cam — closing arguments are set to begin in wi v. Jury deliberations begin in trial of kyle rittenhouse for. Jury instructions, closing arguments in kyle rittenhouse trial: #kylerittenhouse, the kenosha protest shooter trial. Jury deliberations are expected to begin in the trial of kyle rittenhouse, who is charged with killing two people and wounding a third in .
  Watch Live Kyle Rittenhouse Trial Begins Over Kenosha Wisconsin Shooting Youtube from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris To Be Replaced</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-to-be-replaced.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-to-be-replaced.html</guid>
      <description>While most polls show the americans&amp;#039; disapproval of joe biden&amp;#039;s handling of the issue in afghanistan, not many stand behind kamala harris . Gavin newsom (d) announced that he would appoint california secretary of state alex padilla to fill the vacancy and serve . Saying farewell to california, first female, first black vice president, says &amp;#039;hello&amp;#039; to the united states and history. On december 22, 2020, california gov. Gavin newsom of california selected mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sophia Urista Instagram</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/sophia-urista-instagram.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/sophia-urista-instagram.html</guid>
      <description>This recipe is simple, delicious &amp;amp; full of…” sophiaurista. 13/11/2021 · sophia urista has amassed a large following of 58,000 followers on instagram as well. “on the prowl 🐅 for a band name. Reacting to the unforeseen act, several netizens took to twitter to express their disgust. This recipe is simple, delicious &amp;amp; full of flavor, like eating one of my kisses😘 😂 🎥 …
  Qpipfop0au Gfm from biographydaily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trial Of Kyle Rittenhouse Reddit</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/trial-of-kyle-rittenhouse-reddit.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/trial-of-kyle-rittenhouse-reddit.html</guid>
      <description>With the trial finally starting up after a year, some new evidence was presented that shows more of what went down with kyle and rosenbaum. The trial of kyle rittenhouse. Apparently the fbi has been sitting on drone footage of what happened that night this whole time. Posted by 8 days ago. Last summer, as the country reeled from the murder of george floyd, another black man, jacob blake, was shot by police in kenosha, wis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Time Is Lunar Eclipse November 2021</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/what-time-is-lunar-eclipse-november-2021.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/what-time-is-lunar-eclipse-november-2021.html</guid>
      <description>Are you posting on instagram at the right time, on the right day? If you’re in the path of totality—where the moon blocks out 100 percent of the sun—that dark. Whether you prefer the convenience of an electric can opener or you&amp;#039;re perfectly fine with the simplicity of manual models, a can opener is an indispensable kitchen tool you can’t live without unless you plan to never eat canned foods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billy Eppler</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/billy-eppler.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/billy-eppler.html</guid>
      <description>He was the yankees&amp;#039; scouting director before gm brian . He was the general manager of the los . Because when you get the chance to hire a guy who piloted the angels to nary a.500 season with . The mets finally landed on billy eppler. He works for william morris endeavor.
  Angels Hire Yankees Exec Billy Eppler As New Gm Cbssports Com from sports.cbsimg.net  The mets finally landed on billy eppler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halo Halo Infinite</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/halo-halo-infinite.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/halo-halo-infinite.html</guid>
      <description>John junyszek, the community manager for halo at 343 industries, responded to a fan tweeting about a possibly further delay into 2022. But there’s only ever been one true mascot for micro. Laptopmag is supported by its audience. However, we do know it will have some form of microtransactions. The multiplayer mode will run at up to 120fps on xbox series x, and offer capture the flag and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hung Jury</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/hung-jury.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/hung-jury.html</guid>
      <description>This direction is most commonly known as an allen charge. In addition, most jurors have their minds made up going into deliberations, so hung juries are relatively rare. When jurors can’t agree, it’s often called a hung jury or a deadlocked jury. The short answer is that most juries want to come to a verdict. If the jury is hung the trial judge will declare a mistrial.
  Destiny 2 Update Brings Back Hung Jury Sr4 For Season Of The Splicer from static1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Live Trial</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-live-trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-live-trial.html</guid>
      <description>Reckless actions that left other people fearful for their own lives. Aiming it at people, threatening people&amp;#039;s lives. Threatening people&amp;#039;s lives,” binger told the jurors. Provocation charge in closing arguments: Rittenhouse, now 18, could get life in prison if convicted of .
  What We Learned From Opening Testimony In The Kyle Rittenhouse Trial The New York Times from static01.nyt.com  Threatening people&amp;#039;s lives,” binger told the jurors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Lead Singer</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-lead-singer.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-lead-singer.html</guid>
      <description>(wtrf) — singer sophia urista of the band brass against made a quick bathroom break during their florida concert earlier this . Sheridan has 4 jobs listed on their profile. Brass against is known for performing brass renditions of rock songs, but now they are making headlines for another reason: View sheridan brass&amp;#039; profile on linkedin, the world&amp;#039;s largest professional community. According to tmz, sophia urista, the frontwoman for brass against, known for performing brass renditions of rock songs, had been performing a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huntington Brass</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/huntington-brass.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/huntington-brass.html</guid>
      <description>Huntington brass bathroom faucets | sink, tub &amp;amp; shower faucets | all now on sale at tubz.com. Huntington brass specializes in faucets for the kitchen, home bar, and bathroom. Shop for huntington brass at ferguson. Huntington brass st5000c cartridge assembly. Huntington brass is the leading manufacturer of high quality kitchen faucets, widespread lavatory faucets, roman tub fillers, shower systems and bath .
  Huntington Brass 69 Metal Shower P0341429 Sognare Tile Stone Sognare Kitchen Bath from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inciweb</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/inciweb.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/inciweb.html</guid>
      <description>Before you head out on a trip, we recommend you check the newly redesigned inciweb, a website run by several federal agencies — including the u.s. The fire was first reported on monday morning at 6 am that was started by a lightning strike . This new website is the result of collaboration . The system was developed with two primary missions: This map from inciweb, the national interagency fire center&amp;#039;s fire information system, shows multiple wildfires burning around the west on .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Posobiec Twitter</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/jack-posobiec-twitter.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/jack-posobiec-twitter.html</guid>
      <description>He now says he was unaware of his views. Use the following guidelines to determin. Twitter ceo jack dorsey has taken an increasingly aggressive approach to policing the social media platform. Twitter is making some big changes, including a company reorganization, an ad transparency initiative and booting more trolls and spammers from the platform. In a moment of sheer tone deafness, the hacking group ‘ourmine’ hacked into the twitter accounts of twitter ceo jack dorsey, yahoo ceo marissa mayer, and venture capitalist vinod khosla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julius Jones Case</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/julius-jones-case.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/julius-jones-case.html</guid>
      <description>However, his legal team failed to present his alibi at . In the application, he wrote that “while being transferred from an oklahoma city police car to an . Jones was sentenced to death in 2002 for killing paul howell in a suburb of oklahoma city, with the case based largely on a single eyewitness . Can i analyze the case of julius jones?support dr. Howell was gunned down in the driveway of his .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Trial Fox</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-fox.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-fox.html</guid>
      <description>With the sequel about to hit, she talks a blue streak about fame, creepy men, jealous women, and refusing to be a “publicity android.” t. Registration on or use of this site constitutes acceptance of our terms of service and privacy. Some say that writers and thinkers are either hedgehogs or foxes. Listen for the distortion of strategy. On one side is a balanced central vision.
  Iqoiustump6 Ym from trendfool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brass Against</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/the-brass-against.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/the-brass-against.html</guid>
      <description>Brass against is a collective of artists, led and curated by brad hammonds, . That&amp;#039;s not something the rest . Listen to music by brass against on apple music. In a politically challenging era, it&amp;#039;s our time to stand up against the machine. Brass against is collective of artists, led and curated by brad hammonds, who share in the goal of creating brass protest music that calls fans to action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Against Singer Video</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-against-singer-video.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-against-singer-video.html</guid>
      <description>The premiere of the music video for the song she wrote about king, . Find the latest tracks, albums, and images from brass against. She frequently uploads her performance videos on her youtube channel with 12.5k subscribers, which was . Brass against frontwoman sophia urista has been the lead singer of. Video · magazine · events · shop · subscribe · brass against 2020 press, shervin lainez music · hear brass against rage on debut ep of original songs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Prosecutor Gun</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-prosecutor-gun.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-prosecutor-gun.html</guid>
      <description>2 days ago · kyle rittenhouse, right, looks on as the jury is let out of the room during a break during his trail at the kenosha county courthouse in kenosha, wis., on monday, nov. 1 day ago · kyle rittenhouse’s murder trial came to a dramatic end on tuesday, including a bizarre moment a lead prosecutor picked up a rifle. (sean krajacic/the kenosha news via ap, pool) previous post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Moon</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/blood-moon.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/blood-moon.html</guid>
      <description>Mad designer imagine to be able to execute amazing tasks in some impossible places, like working on the surface of the moon in cyborging devices assembled there and experiencing looking to earth, will that be possible? Stand with your feet spread wide, your left foot facing to the left and your right toes slightly in. How was the moon made? If you&amp;#039;re in north america, south america, parts of western europe or africa, you can catch a glimpse of what people are calling this post contains references to products from one or more of our advertisers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Against Pees On Fan Video</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-against-pees-on-fan-video.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-against-pees-on-fan-video.html</guid>
      <description>There are many fans after this incident who shared their views over the clip . Watch our show &amp;amp; entertainment videos below: But the jet was so strong that most of the urine ended up on the fan. Brass against singer pees on fan onstage (video). Brass against addresses shocking moment lead singer sophia urista.
  30h B0ilyxylsm from www.nme.com  Brass against singer pees on fan onstage (video).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julius Jones Dna</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/julius-jones-dna.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/julius-jones-dna.html</guid>
      <description>A panel has recommended that julius jones&amp;#039;s sentence in a 1999 murder. Julius jones was 19 years old when he was arrested for murder in oklahoma. Despite an alibi, no matching dna found at the crime scene, and having tons of celebrity support, julius jones is still serving out a death . The dna found on the bandana conclusively showed by 1 in 110million, that jones was wearing the bandana that was in his room, wrapped in the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/oklahoma.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/oklahoma.html</guid>
      <description>Get the latest breaking news, sports, entertainment and obituaries in oklahoma city, ok from oklahoman.com. Oklahoma county is in the process of developing a plan to utilize the american rescue plan. We are building a state where businesses grow and communities thrive. Campus calendar | see events. Recognized for academic leadership, high employment rates and christian character, you are wanted at oc and great things are expected of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singer Urinates On Fan Video</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/singer-urinates-on-fan-video.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/singer-urinates-on-fan-video.html</guid>
      <description>When the summer heat strikes, breaking out a fan is one of the few things you can do to keep cool. With overwatch‘s colorful cast of characters, it’s not too hard to imagine a world where they came to li. Stressing out over which *nsync video i. Obviously, this test doesn&amp;#039;t hurt. Watch allure cover star billy porter surprise a superfan who has been deeply moved by the visibility of his rise to fame and what it means to the qtpoc (queer and trans people of color) community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alzheimer Nasal Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/alzheimer-nasal-vaccine.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/alzheimer-nasal-vaccine.html</guid>
      <description>Korin miller is a health and lifestyle journalist who has been published in the. For this reason, the vaccination is of. See what others have said about zolmitriptan (nasal)(nasal), including the effectiveness, ease of use and side effects. I had several migraines a m. Zolmitriptan (nasal)(nasal) received an overall rating of 10 out of 10 stars from 4 reviews.
  Amyloid B Immunisation For Alzheimer S Disease The Lancet Neurology from els-jbs-prod-cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris And Willie Brown</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-and-willie-brown.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-and-willie-brown.html</guid>
      <description>Those who can trace their political lineage directly, or indirectly, to phil burton include nancy pelosi, gavin newsom and willie brown. I hope san francisco takes on my style and my attitude. &amp;#039;historically, the vice presidency has often ended up being a dead end&amp;#039; The latest breaking news, comment and features from the independent. Gavin newsom will appoint a successor to sen.
  Kamala Harris Learned How To Become A Political Brawler In San Francisco The Washington Post from arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November Full Moon</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/november-full-moon.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/november-full-moon.html</guid>
      <description>It is also called frost moon and mourning moon, depending on the winter solstice. Depending on the winter solstice, the november full moon is also known as the frost moon or mourning moon. The full moon after next will be friday morning, nov. 03/11/2020 · the november full moon is known as the beaver moon since beavers typically build their winter homes during this time of the year. The north american beaver has named the november full moon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bellingham Washington Flooding</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/bellingham-washington-flooding.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/bellingham-washington-flooding.html</guid>
      <description>Learn how to protect your home from the dangers and damage of flooding. Most homeowners with flood insurance still get it from the federal government. I&amp;#039;ve been watching all of the devastating stories on the news about families who are losing their homes to the midwest floods, and i&amp;#039;ve been thinking about my own protection. Most homes aren’t covered for the #1 natural disaster, flooding. How is this different than the aftermath most homeowners face after a flood?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full.moon November 2021</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/full-moon-november-2021.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/full-moon-november-2021.html</guid>
      <description>Thanks to &amp;#039;the old farmer’s almanac&amp;#039; and nasa, we know when to expect a full moon each month in 2021. Rumors surrounding the coolest new smartphones, many of which. However, this virus is still impacting countries and communities in an unpredictable way as infections co. From tablets that let you surf the net to readers devoted solel. In november of that year, all of that work precipitated some exciting news:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kind Of Advice Crossword</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kind-of-advice-crossword.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kind-of-advice-crossword.html</guid>
      <description>21 rows · the crossword solver found 20 answers to the type of advice crossword clue. A bird eaten by friend of father. Movie theater groups (1) contract … Written by bible september 15, 2021. Synonyms, crossword answers and other related words for advice we hope that the following list of synonyms for the word advice will help you to finish your crossword today.
  Printable Crossword Puzzles With Answers Reader S Digest from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kruger Fire Map</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kruger-fire-map.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kruger-fire-map.html</guid>
      <description>Cbs4’s dillon thomas was first to report the information. A map below shows where the two. At last report, the blaze was 115 acres with 11% containment. Wildfire erupts in estes park. By 10 a.m., it was estimated at 75 acres.
  Sanparks Org from   1 day ago · map of kruger fire, estes park nov 16, 2021 nov 16, 2021 updated 48 min ago; 23 hours ago · estes park, colo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden Kamala Harris</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/biden-kamala-harris.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/biden-kamala-harris.html</guid>
      <description>A damning report, a pushback and a possible crisis in the white house — the ride for us president joe biden just got bumpier amid an alleged . Together, joe biden and kamala harris offered restoration and renewal in a single ticket. Kolam is a traditional south indian rangoli that is made with rice flour by women to invite health and prosperity into their homes. She was elected vice president after a lifetime of public service, having been elected district attorney of san francisco, california attorney general, and .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Motors</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/lucid-motors.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/lucid-motors.html</guid>
      <description>Copyright © 2021 investorplace media, llc. This growth company has competitive technology and the cash needed to scale. A merger will value lucid motors at $11.75 billion and provide the startup with $4.4 billion in cash. Just like any other vehicle you can buy. Today, cciv stock is on the move as investors continue to anticipate what could be announced at tomorrow&amp;#039;s shareholder call.
  Lucid Launches Production Of The Air Electric Sedan Electrive Com from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunar Eclipse 2021 New Mexico</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/lunar-eclipse-2021-new-mexico.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/lunar-eclipse-2021-new-mexico.html</guid>
      <description>We believe everyone should be able to make financial decis. When you purchase through links on our site, we. Published on 6/4/2020 at 6:51 pm there&amp;#039;s good news and bad news for lovers of celes. 27, we&amp;#039;ll be treated to a supermoon eclipse. Signing out of account, standby.
  Lunar Eclipse Today These Indian Cities Will See Celestial Phenomenon Science News from akm-img-a-in.tosshub.com  We believe everyone should be able to make financial decis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Monkey</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-monkey.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-monkey.html</guid>
      <description>See reviews that mention best place for bowling in dxb. Brass monkey is a polished bowling and arcade experience. nicholas t. Gumpendorfer strasse 71 ,1060 vienna. Provided to youtube by universal music group brass monkey · beastie boys licensed to ill ℗ 1986 umg recordings, inc. Brass monkey add to list share.
  Brass Monkey Drink A Couple Cooks from www.acouplecooks.com  Brass monkey is a polished bowling and arcade experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iman David Bowie</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/iman-david-bowie.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/iman-david-bowie.html</guid>
      <description>Christie brinkley shares the story of how her child helped iman and david bowie have a baby of their own. Carmaker&amp;#039;s design chief on the man who fell to earth. I only have three heroes in my lifetime: David bowie was one of the most legendary performers across pop, rock, and alternative genres. Jonathan barnbrook&amp;#039;s blackstar design for bowie&amp;#039;s final album in a move that will delight and inspire david bowie fans around the world, london design studio barnbrook has released the design elements for the musician&amp;#039;s last alb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is There A Verdict In The Kyle Rittenhouse Trial</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/is-there-a-verdict-in-the-kyle-rittenhouse-trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/is-there-a-verdict-in-the-kyle-rittenhouse-trial.html</guid>
      <description>The kenosha sheriff&amp;#039;s department said it understands and recognizes the anxiety surrounding the kyle rittenhouse trial and has made . Jurors haven&amp;#039;t reached a verdict yet, after about eight hours of deliberation tuesday. The judge&amp;#039;s instruction on lighter charges was seen as a win for the prosecution. Jurors in the kyle rittenhouse trial spent all day tuesday deliberating without returning a verdict, and have informed the court they will .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Protest</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-protest.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-protest.html</guid>
      <description>25, ahead of the third night of protests, rittenhouse, then 17, drove from his home in antioch, ill., across the state line into . Rittenhouse says protesters threatened to kill him. Under questioning from his own attorney, rittenhouse said he was walking toward a car . (ap) — kyle rittenhouse took the stand in his murder trial wednesday, testifying about how he shot three men during a protest .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Verdict Watch</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-verdict-watch.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-verdict-watch.html</guid>
      <description>With jurors now deliberating in the kyle rittenhouse trial, many are anxiously awaiting a verdict in a polarizing case that has garnered nationwide attention. Kyle rittenhouse pulls numbers of alternate jurors. Embed more news videos the judge had rittenhouse pull the numbers of the six alternates from the drum just after 9 a.m., and the. 18 hours ago · the jury in the trial of kyle rittenhouse will begin deliberations today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Brilliant Diamond Shining Pearl</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/pokemon-brilliant-diamond-shining-pearl.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/pokemon-brilliant-diamond-shining-pearl.html</guid>
      <description>You’ll visit many different locations in the sinnoh region, while striving to become the champion of the. Rich in nature and with mount coronet towering at its heart, sinnoh is a land of many myths passed down through the ages. 1 day ago · pokemon brilliant diamond and shining pearl launch for nintendo switch this friday, and pokemon go is celebrating their arrival with a special event from nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sophia Urista Pees On Fan Video</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/sophia-urista-pees-on-fan-video.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/sophia-urista-pees-on-fan-video.html</guid>
      <description>During a set at welcome to rockville on thursday night, singer sophia urista pulled down her pants on stage and peed on a ( . During the welcome to rockville festival at the daytona international speedway, florida, sophia urista from band . A police report was reportedly filed in daytona, fla., after brass against singer sophia urista called a fan onto the stage, . Brass against have apologised after singer sophia urista peed on a fan&amp;#039;s face during a performance over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queen Elizabeth Ii</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/queen-elizabeth-ii.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/queen-elizabeth-ii.html</guid>
      <description>“the queen today received general sir nick carter for an audience. 17/11/2021 · queen elizabeth ii was back on her feet performing royal duties following a recent health scare that led to her hospitalization. 6 hours ago · queen elizabeth ii is back in action 00:45. London — buckingham palace released video on wednesday of queen elizabeth ii holding a meeting with a government official at her home at windsor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapchat</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/snapchat.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/snapchat.html</guid>
      <description>Unless you’ve been hiding under a rock, you’ve probably heard someone mention the social network/chat app snapchat. Snapchat, perhaps the most youthful of all the social media channels, is remarkably receptive to. Snapchat is all about the mo. Khallil’s career/life is definitely wild. No, i&amp;#039;m not talking about the recent update that allowed users to leave each other video voicemails (though that was pretty cool).
  5 Snapchat Statistics That Prove Its Power from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jess King Wife</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/jess-king-wife.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/jess-king-wife.html</guid>
      <description>Meet helen king, a live yes! Gail cohen &amp;amp; gilbert debenedetti though history is la. Sign up and get early access. She became more involved in religious activity. The couple, who are in their late seventies, are reportedly responding to treatment.
  Meeting Jess King Physical Space In A Digital World By Davidjmillerphd Medium from miro.medium.com  The civil rights leader, baptist minister, and former presidential candi. Think you may have arthritis?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is There A Verdict In The Rittenhouse Trial</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/is-there-a-verdict-in-the-rittenhouse-trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/is-there-a-verdict-in-the-rittenhouse-trial.html</guid>
      <description>The final verdict has not yet been reached. Louis allwood 11th nov 2021, 08:30. Et today, here&amp;#039;s a look at the five felony counts against rittenhouse. 16 hours ago · the jury at kyle rittenhouse&amp;#039;s murder trial deliberated a full day on tuesday without reaching a verdict over whether he was the instigator in a night of bloodshed in kenosha or a concerned. The panel of 18 jurors, eight men and 10 women, will be narrowed down to the 12 by a random drawing using a raffle tumbler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Trial Live Feed</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-live-feed.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-live-feed.html</guid>
      <description>A few months later, though, thousands watched as he streamed footage from the wisconsin streets where kyle rittenhouse shot three people. Rittenhouse is expected to say that he . In addition to counts of intentional, reckless and attempted homicide and reckless endangerment, . You can read about what . Our live coverage has ended.
  Ecdrl8tlusoy3m from i.ytimg.com  Manipulated video evidence to make it more helpful to prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Full Moon</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/next-full-moon.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/next-full-moon.html</guid>
      <description>If we try to make an. All about the astrological moon: Women&amp;#039;s health may earn commission from the links on this page, but we only feature products we believe in. Almost 50 years ago, on july 20, 1969, the spacecraft apollo 11 safely landed astronauts on the moon’s surface for the first time. Researchers say it&amp;#039;s not outside the realm.
  When Is The Next Full Moon Date Of August 2021 Full Moon In Uk What Is A Sturgeon Moon And How To See It The Scotsman from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luna Eclipse November 2021</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/luna-eclipse-november-2021.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/luna-eclipse-november-2021.html</guid>
      <description>Duration of the partial lunar eclipse is 3 hours 28 minutes and 24 seconds, longest lunar eclipse in 580 years india will experience a total lunar eclipse on november 8, 2022. A full moon occurs when the sun in scorpio forms an opposition to the moon in taurus. This partial lunar eclipse, the last lunar eclipse of 2021, is visible from north and south america, australia, and parts of europe and asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can A Judge Overrule A Jury</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/can-a-judge-overrule-a-jury.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/can-a-judge-overrule-a-jury.html</guid>
      <description>However, the judge denied his request to sequester the jury. 👀 looking at you, people who don&amp;#039;t use their turn signal. Even if your case is eligible for a jury trial, it&amp;#039;s often better to tell it to the judge. The question is, whatcha gonna do about it? Both the defense and prosecution try to obtain favorable jurors, while the court is supposed to ensure that the process is fair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Kyle Rittenhouse Verdict</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/when-kyle-rittenhouse-verdict.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/when-kyle-rittenhouse-verdict.html</guid>
      <description>Represented by zuma press, inc. Closing arguments for kyle rittenhouse&amp;#039;s trial are scheduled for monday, november 14, 2021 in kenosha, wisconsin. 1 day ago · kyle rittenhouse, now 18 years old, faces charges of intentional, reckless and attempted homicide, and reckless endangerment. What is the kyle rittenhouse final verdict? What is the kyle rittenhouse final verdict?
  K Xdetrgoul6xm from www.gannett-cdn.com  The final verdict has not yet been reached.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Lunar Eclipse November 2021</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/full-lunar-eclipse-november-2021.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/full-lunar-eclipse-november-2021.html</guid>
      <description>This taurus lunar eclipse will align with the notorious fixed star algol in the head of medusa. This year, falling at the tail end of scorpio season, an intense new cycle kicks off with a lunar eclipse and full moon in hardheaded, sensual fixed earth sign taurus.ruled by venus — the planet of love, beauty, and money — this lunar event hosted by the bull is sure to shine a light on evolving relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solar Eclipse 2021</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/solar-eclipse-2021.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/solar-eclipse-2021.html</guid>
      <description>A bookworm is happiest when they’re surrounded by books — both old and new. But are they really free? Check out our picks for the best solar chargers. If you missed today’s solar eclipse, fear not, there wi. 2020 was an excellent year.
  Ring Of Fire Solar Eclipse How To Watch What Time Is It Livestream Cnet from www.cnet.com  But are they really free? If you’ve been shopping around for a solar panel system, you’ve probably heard at least one company advertis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staples Center</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/staples-center.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/staples-center.html</guid>
      <description>Vaccines, boosters &amp;amp; 3rd d. You can also visit the company website, use online maps, visit an online director. Staples hold two or more objects together by punching through the material and bending back on themselves. There are a number of ways to find the staples nearest store, beginning with entering the query in a search box and allowing your device to use your location. Stapled hemorrhoidopexy involves stapling the last section of the large bowel, which reduces the supply of blood to the hemorrhoids and gradually shrinks them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Brass Against</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/twitter-brass-against.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/twitter-brass-against.html</guid>
      <description>Sophia urista video brass against singer pees on fan onstage, leaves twitter scandalized: 14/11/2021 · brass against have issued a response via twitter. Kelly remix coming soon,” another person added. We had a great time last night at welcome to rockville. The latest tweets from @brassagainst
  Shashi Tharoor On Twitter The Udf Released Its Election Manifesto Today In Thiruvananthapuram W All Coalition Leaders Inckerala Top Brass On Stage I Stressed That Our Proposed Welfare Measures Would Be Funded By from pbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Lunar Eclipse</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/full-lunar-eclipse.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/full-lunar-eclipse.html</guid>
      <description>The third column lists the eclipse type which is either total, partial, or penumbral. A concise summary of all lunar eclipses from 2021 through 2030 is presented in the table below. The first column gives the calendar date of the instant of greatest eclipse.the second column td of greatest eclipse is the terrestrial dynamical time of greatest eclipse. The november 2021 full moon has a lot of significance in astrology and this is because there will be a full moon lunar eclipse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Trial Information</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-information.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-information.html</guid>
      <description>Kyle rittenhouse waited for the jury to enter the room to continue testifying during his trial at the kenosha county courthouse in kenosha, . The homicide trial of kyle rittenhouse is a political powder keg, pulling together several explosive issues including violence, protest and . The 12 jurors&amp;#039; day concludes after roughly eight hours of deliberation, during which they did not request additional information from lawyers of . The wisconsin jury that will decide whether or not to convict accused kenosha shooter kyle rittenhouse may be allowed to consider lesser .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Is Rittenhouse Verdict</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/when-is-rittenhouse-verdict.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/when-is-rittenhouse-verdict.html</guid>
      <description>1 day ago · kyle rittenhouse, now 18 years old, faces charges of intentional, reckless and attempted homicide, and reckless endangerment. 4 hours ago · the jurors in the trial of kyle rittenhouse resumed deliberations this morning, according to a pool reporter in court. 12/11/2021 · kyle rittenhouse&amp;#039;s mother stressed that her son&amp;#039;s verdict is in the hands of the jury ahead of a ruling on what charges the judge will allow for consideration in the wisconsin murder trial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replacing Kamala Harris</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/replacing-kamala-harris.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/replacing-kamala-harris.html</guid>
      <description>Gavin newsom of california selected mr. Who will california governor gavin newsom . The democrat will be formally replaced by california&amp;#039;s secretary of state, following her resignation. Saying farewell to california, first female, first black vice president, says &amp;#039;hello&amp;#039; to the united states and history. Kamala harris will soon give up her seat in the senate to assume the role as vice president.
  Alex Padilla To Replace Kamala Harris In The Us Senate California Governor Newstrack English 1 from media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Is The Kyle Rittenhouse Verdict</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/when-is-the-kyle-rittenhouse-verdict.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/when-is-the-kyle-rittenhouse-verdict.html</guid>
      <description>The jury in the wisconsin murder trial of kyle rittenhouse ended their first day of deliberations on tuesday without reaching a verdict, . Kyle rittenhouse shot three people during chaotic protests in august 2020. The judge dropped that charge monday after arguments . He faces multiple felony charges of homicide and recklessly endangering the safety of others, along with one misdemeanor count of possession of . He has pleaded not guilty to all counts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Kyle Rittenhouse On Trial</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/why-is-kyle-rittenhouse-on-trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/why-is-kyle-rittenhouse-on-trial.html</guid>
      <description>1 day ago · madison, wis. Closing arguments were held monday and the jury will now decide the case. 10/11/2021 · understand the trial of kyle rittenhouse kyle rittenhouse, 18, is on trial for the killing of two people protesting the police shooting of a black man in kenosha, wis. 15/11/2021 · the homicide trial of kyle rittenhouse is nearing its end. 2 hours ago · an anxious america awaits as the jury continues its deliberations in the kyle rittenhouse murder trial in connection to last year&amp;#039;s shootings in wisconsin&amp;#039;s kenosha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estes Park Fire Today</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/estes-park-fire-today.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/estes-park-fire-today.html</guid>
      <description>A small wildfire broke out tuesday morning near kruger rock in larimer county, which is about two and a half miles south of downtown estes . The kruger rock fire that started just southeast of estes park. The internal page to reflect the current situation and direct folks to . (cnn) a wildfire that sparked in colorado on tuesday quickly grew in size, prompting evacuations in the town of estes park, near rocky .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Tanker</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/air-tanker.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/air-tanker.html</guid>
      <description>However, for those who have been collecting airmiles redeem points, you know the process can become overwhelming. On the other side, par. But do you know how to get those coveted. Whether you&amp;#039;re installing a heating, ventilation and air conditioning (hvac) unit in a new home or upgrading your existing system, it&amp;#039;s important to research your options. The air miles scheme is a great idea.
  Erickson Aero Tanker Wins 70 5 Million Federal Firefighting Contract from media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Moon 2021 November</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/full-moon-2021-november.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/full-moon-2021-november.html</guid>
      <description>Rumors surrounding the coolest new smartphones, many of which. The full moon in aquarius is a rare astrological blue moon. Out of all the phases of the lunar cycle, full moons are the en. Astrology allow your imagination to run wild. Thanks to &amp;#039;the old farmer’s almanac&amp;#039; and nasa, we know when to expect a full moon each month in 2021.
  Cara Author At Fullmoonology from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris Approval</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-approval.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-approval.html</guid>
      <description>November 15, 2021 | mike enright &amp;#039;88 (clas), university communications. The latest tweets from kamala harris (@kamalaharris). Joe biden the former vice president wants to build on the obama legacy, with healthcare being a top priority. Why are kamala harris&amp;#039; approval ratings lower than biden&amp;#039;s? In the face of the pandemic, biden has .
  Underwater Polls Suggest Kamala Harris Least Popular Vice President Since 1970s World News Wionews Com from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse November 19 2021</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/eclipse-november-19-2021.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/eclipse-november-19-2021.html</guid>
      <description>This is a partial lunar eclipse. 19/11/2021 · the moon is full in taurus on november 19, 2021, at 3:58 am est. It will be visible from the americas, north europe, eastern asia, australia, and the pacific. A partial lunar eclipse will occur on friday, november 19, 2021. At the moment of greatest eclipse, at around 9:03 a.m.
  666vruygdfgsm from images.livemint.com  Map of partial lunar eclipse on november 19, 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julius Jones Oklahoma</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/julius-jones-oklahoma.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/julius-jones-oklahoma.html</guid>
      <description>Granting jones clemency will reduce his death sentence to life in prison with the possibility of parole for the 1999 murder of oklahoma city . Julius jones is still scheduled to be executed in oklahoma on november 18, 2021, despite maintaining his innocence and compelling evidence that he was . Jones, 41, has spent more than half of his life in prison after he was charged and convicted of the murder of paul howell during a 1999 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Rittenhouse Verdict When</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-verdict-when.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kyle-rittenhouse-verdict-when.html</guid>
      <description>Kyle rittenhouse shot three people during chaotic protests in august 2020. Rittenhouse, then 17, shot two men to death and wounded a third . Kyle rittenhouse&amp;#039;s defense team begins closing arguments in his murder trial. The trial of kyle rittenhouse has lasted for two weeks, with dozens of witnesses, photo evidence and video clips, as well as testimony from . Jurors are no longer considering charging rittenhouse with illegally carrying a weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahmaud Arbery Trial</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/ahmaud-arbery-trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/ahmaud-arbery-trial.html</guid>
      <description>And various organizations list the open clinical trials. The division of cancer prevention (dcp) conducts and supports research to determine a person&amp;#039;s risk of cancer and to find ways to reduce the risk. The.gov means it’s official.federal government websites often end in.gov o. The process of assigning patients to these groups by chance is c. This helps people find ones that may be appropriate for them.
  V26hasrzy7u4am from a9p9n2x2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meteor Shower Tonight</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/meteor-shower-tonight.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/meteor-shower-tonight.html</guid>
      <description>Northern taurids will be followed by partial lunar eclipse. Find an area with a clear view of the horizon and away from trees and . Delta aquarid meteor shower is set to dazzle the night sky this coming week. However, you should still give it a . · in ideal conditions you can see 10 to 15 meteors at the peak of the shower .
  Leonid Meteor Shower Visible In Indian Skies from im.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden Polls</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/biden-polls.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/biden-polls.html</guid>
      <description>When election season rolls around, it might be hard to figure out where to go to vote if it&amp;#039;s your first time, you&amp;#039;ve recently moved or your precinct has changed venues for election day. Tumbling over the edges of containers and spilling down the sides of hanging baskets, bidens looks like a colorful floral waterfall. Here are three ways you can, via stories, a page, and groups. Want to know what your instagram followers like or don&amp;#039;t like?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singer Pees On Stage</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/singer-pees-on-stage.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/singer-pees-on-stage.html</guid>
      <description>Is that young jeezy mad in a hennessy ad? “so we might as well make a show out of it.”. Sophia urista, the frontwoman of brass against, shocked crowds with the crude display at the welcome to rockville festival in daytona. “get my man with the can on his head ready, because we’re going. The frontwoman of brass against made headlines when the rock …
  Water Or Urine Kiss Gene Simmons Explains Onstage Peeing Video from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Bowie</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/david-bowie.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/david-bowie.html</guid>
      <description>They met on a blind. In an interview with harper&amp;#039;s bazaar in january, iman talked about how much of a presence her husband still is in her life. At age 13, inspired by the jazz of the london west end, he picked up the saxophone and called up ronnie ross for lessons. Never look back, walk tall, act fine. We never bothered to scream, when your mask came off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meteor Shower November 2021</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/meteor-shower-november-2021.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/meteor-shower-november-2021.html</guid>
      <description>They&amp;#039;re a must if your grooming routine calls for shaving in the shower. The best shower curtain liner prevents splashes, puddles, and mildew in your bathing area. Never miss a night of stargazing again. From floral designs to minimalist styles, these are the best shower curtains. Check out our roundup of 23 gorgeous picks, including both classic and modern shower curtains.
  Meteor Shower from   Confidence, community, and joy our editors independently research, test, and recommend the best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sophia Urista Peed</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/sophia-urista-peed.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/sophia-urista-peed.html</guid>
      <description>Sophia urista from the band brass against pulled an unbelievable stunt while covering &amp;#039;wake up&amp;#039; by rage against the machine. On thursday, november 11, 2021, sophia urista made headlines after an incident at a concert in which she peed on a fan. A rising rockstar has been received a new title after her immoral and bizarre act. Sophia urista has been trending all over the internet not because of her stunning performance but due to an outrageous stunt she pulled on .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cspan</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/cspan.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/cspan.html</guid>
      <description>After words with ben shapiro. And most importantly, one step ahead of the rest! David wasserman discusses campaign 2022.
  C Span Live Stream C Span Org from static.c-span.org  David wasserman discusses campaign 2022. And most importantly, one step ahead of the rest! After words with ben shapiro. After words with ben shapiro. And most importantly, one step ahead of the rest! David wasserman discusses campaign 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Large Fleets Crossword Clue</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/large-fleets-crossword-clue.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/large-fleets-crossword-clue.html</guid>
      <description>Limit close contact with others, staying about ___ feet apart. (other definitions for armada that i&amp;#039;ve seen before include fleet of armed ships . 1 a fleet of warships, especially with reference to the spanish armada. Avoid large _____ of people. Every issue of games magazine contains a large crossword with a double clue list, under the title the world&amp;#039;s most .
  Largest Living Antelopes Crossword Clue Archives Laxcrossword Com from laxcrossword.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rittenhouse Trial Verdict Date</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/rittenhouse-trial-verdict-date.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/rittenhouse-trial-verdict-date.html</guid>
      <description>Jury deliberations begin tuesday in the trial of kyle rittenhouse, the armed illinois teenager who killed two people and wounded another . Date of verdict on kenosha shooting, who were the victims, and what did he do? Rittenhouse, 18, is charged with . The jury deliberated a full day on tuesday without reaching a verdict at kyle rittenhouse&amp;#039;s murder trial after two weeks of testimony in . The jury did not reach a verdict.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Tennis Player Peng Shuai</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/chinese-tennis-player-peng-shuai.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/chinese-tennis-player-peng-shuai.html</guid>
      <description>Naomi osaka has joined a growing number of tennis players and officials asking for answers about peng shuai, the chinese athlete who hasn&amp;#039;t . World tennis champion naomi osaka has become the latest athlete to voice concerns over the whereabouts of chinese tennis player peng shuai. The women&amp;#039;s tennis association has called for a full, transparent investigation into an allegation of sexual assault made by chinese player . Peng shuai has so far been regarded as china&amp;#039;s model tennis player, in whose achievements the leadership in beijing liked to bask.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Watch Kyle Rittenhouse Trial</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/how-to-watch-kyle-rittenhouse-trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/how-to-watch-kyle-rittenhouse-trial.html</guid>
      <description>The defense lawyer argued that rittenhouse is the . The latest tiktok trend is watching a homicide trial. While court is in session, you can watch proceedings live below. Jury deliberations begin tuesday in the trial of kyle rittenhouse, the armed illinois teenager who killed two people and wounded another . Kenosha, wisconsin — attorneys are set to make closing arguments at kyle rittenhouse&amp;#039;s trial in the shootings of three men during street .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris Fired</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-fired.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-fired.html</guid>
      <description>The searching query that underscored the watergate scandal is . Kamala harris must be fired from her role overseeing the border crisis. I wasn&amp;#039;t trying to be malicious. She is the first female vice . Khadijah abdurahman said on medium she was fired from her role as visiting lecturer and researcher at cornell tech by associate professor .
  Cleveland Radio Station Fires Anchor For Calling Kamala Harris Colored from s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco 49Ers Los Angeles Rams</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/san-francisco-49ers-los-angeles-rams.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/san-francisco-49ers-los-angeles-rams.html</guid>
      <description>The rams have a lot of work to do as the franchise prepares to move from st. Print rates start at only $80/month and online rates at $15/month. Los angeles and san francisco are feuding over their latest west coast rivalry: Which city will become home to star wars cre. Here are our favorite tips.
  Cop1kwl2yim0pm from media.gettyimages.com  The rams have a lot of work to do as the franchise prepares to move from st.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Moon Eclipse</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/blood-moon-eclipse.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/blood-moon-eclipse.html</guid>
      <description>~the saga of harald hardrade, c.103. 19 won’t have an equal for another 648 years. A total or full … Et, a partial lunar eclipse will occur instead of your regularly scheduled full moon. This rare phenomenon happens when the sun, earth, and the moon are out of alignment.
  Get Ready For A Rare Super Blue Blood Moon Eclipse Science Aaas from www.science.org  The phenomenon has a spooky name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urista Pees</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/urista-pees.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/urista-pees.html</guid>
      <description>The members of brass against were just as shocked as festival goers when singer sophia urista peed on the face of a fan during their set at . Brass against singer sophia urista pees on a male fan&amp;#039;s face during live show. A rising rockstar has been received a new title after her immoral and bizarre act. A fan filed the report after complaining about sophia urista&amp;#039;s obscene stage antics at 2021&amp;#039;s welcome to rockville festival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donita Sparks</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/donita-sparks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/donita-sparks.html</guid>
      <description>Stream get to know donita sparks by good night stories for rebel girls: Whether she&amp;#039;s on stage playing her smirking brand of rock &amp;#039;n&amp;#039; roll in her notorious group, l7, . Meet the awesome rock singer, songwriter, and guitarist of the band l7, donita sparks. Select from 252 premium donita sparks of the highest quality. Interviews, features and/or performances archived at npr music.
  Donita Sparks Of L7 Eating Fried Banana With Members Of The Cosmic Psychos In 1992 Or 93 R Oldschoolcool from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris Joe Biden Rift</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-joe-biden-rift.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-joe-biden-rift.html</guid>
      <description>Joe biden, kamala harris offer unified front amid talk of serious rift. 28 oct 2021, 2:55 pm ist Harris’ staff say he is being sidelined, while the president’s team says harris is playing with the american people. In such a situation, it is believed that harris can be … Mr biden&amp;#039;s spokeswoman, jen psaki, said ms harris was a vital partner to the.
  Sc Xhaqmhvrgem from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Stitt</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kevin-stitt.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kevin-stitt.html</guid>
      <description>Meanwhile, several local pastors and antoinette jones said they had hoped to persuade stitt to consider his own christian faith and morals and grant clemency for julius jones. We are here just to ask the governor to make the right decision, to accept the decision made by the parole board, and that he make his … Governor stitt is leading the state with a vision to become top ten in critical categories, from government accountability to job growth, infrastructure, education and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Against The Machine</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-against-the-machine.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-against-the-machine.html</guid>
      <description>Here is a look at brass and other alloys in terms of chemicals solutions and mixtures. Country living editors select each product featured. Michael wurm, jr., the talented diying, decorating. Here is a look at brass and other alloys in terms of chemicals solutions and mixtures. Learn the best way to clean brass candlesticks and keep your brass beauties full of their vintage shine.
  Qav Tvhkzkqkjm from exclaim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch Rittenhouse Trial</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/watch-rittenhouse-trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/watch-rittenhouse-trial.html</guid>
      <description>Opening statements for the upcoming murder trial of kyle rittenhouse, 18, is scheduled to begin tuesday, nov. Closing arguments in the trial of kyle rittenhouse, the teenager who shot three people in the aftermath of demonstrations in kenosha, wis., in august 2020, are. 2 in kenosha county, wisconsin. 4 hours ago · the jurors in the trial of kyle rittenhouse resumed deliberations this morning, according to a pool reporter in court.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris Supreme Court</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-supreme-court.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/kamala-harris-supreme-court.html</guid>
      <description>In the united states, democracy relies on maintaining a balance of power between three key branches: In attacking her record on crime policy, her critics are ignoring how politics actually works. Holding the balance of an entire d. Despite the barriers, despite the pain, kamala harris becomes the first woma. After president donald trump nominated amy coney barrett for ruth bader ginsburg&amp;#039;s former seat on the supreme court, democratic presidential and vice presidential candidates joe biden and kamala harris were quick to strongly oppose barret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porsche 718 Cayman Gt4 Rs</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/porsche-718-cayman-gt4-rs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/porsche-718-cayman-gt4-rs.html</guid>
      <description>Our latest addition to the motorsport family is ready to roar. The 2022 porsche 718 cayman gt4 rs sheds veil, and the company claims that the 718 range flagship can show 100 kmph from a standstill in . The cayman gt4 rs has got tons of aero modifications and the engine from the 911 gt3. 2022 porsche 718 gt4 rs is the ultimate cayman. A whole host of upgrades combine to take the cayman gt4 to new levels, creating quite the performance car in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Onion</title>
      <link>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-onion.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harryalollis.github.io/harry/post/brass-onion.html</guid>
      <description>Order food online at the brass onion, overland park with tripadvisor: The global community for designers and creative . View the brass onion&amp;#039;s november 2021 deals and menus. Support your local restaurants with . The brass onion is definitely a wonderful place to go for lunch or dinner.
  The Brass Onion Anand Vihar New Delhi Zomato from b.zmtcdn.com  The brass onion | 17 followers on linkedin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
